What ?
- All the cops have wooden legs ! - They sure do !
- All right , hold on ! - What is it ? !
Flat tire ! Hold on !
Oh , man .
All right , I 'm gonna find a place to pull over .
Excuse me .
Hey , I like this place .
Maybe we could build some houses ,
just like Gilligan 's Island .
Gilligan 's Island ?
After all that 's happened , Annie ,
what 's wrong with going home ?
Dad ...
- vacation was fine . - Yeah , fine .
Let 's face it , Annie ,
it 's just not the way that it was .
Dad , Mom 's been dead for two years .
It 's the way it is .
We have lift-off .
Honey , look , why don 't you just hit the cooler ,
get yourself some pop ?
But stay close , okay , ' cause I want to fix this tire
and get on home .
Hey , don 't go down there , kid .
There 's all kinds of wild animals and shit .
- Who do you belong to ? - Who do you belong to ?
Hey ! Hey , you ! Hands off !
Are you some kind of a pervert or something ?
Johnny , you know better than that .
You don 't even know this guy .
Hey , hey , wait a minute . I don 't know you either , okay ?
He almost went over the edge .
There could be badgers or something down there .
Throw it .
Come on , throw it .
Well , throw it .
Go back , come on .
Wow , bald and flat .
I feel for you , man .
Sometimes life really sucks , doesn 't it ?
Looks like you just bought me a tournament Frisbee , dude .
I can get it back . No sweat .
Come on . What , are you guys standing guard ? Let 's go .
Come on , guys , let 's go the other way , okay ?
Johnny , come on .
Ah , ha !
I told you .
Was I right , or was I right ?
No playing here !
You kids oughta know better than ...
wait .
You hear it ?
It could be anywhere around here .
Above us , behind us ,
or in the ground .
Do you think this is some kind of joke ?
You think this is some kind of game ? !
They 're hungry . All they do is eat .
You got to keep a weathered eye out all the time !
If you don 't watch every minute ... then wham !
Then it 's too late .
Who are you ?
Any of you ever hear of a place called Grover 's Bend ?
It 's a real town with real people .
Now , in 1984 ...
I was riding my bicycle
and I looked up .
I saw this thing in the sky .
Call the Army . They 're here !
- Who ? - Who ? !
Them !
On Earth
I was just a big nobody .
Up in space I am somebody .
Charlle bounty hunter .
Yeah , " Charlie bounty hunter . "
Dad 's all torn up and Mom 's got like
a harpoon thing in her neck , and they 're getting bigger .
You 're not from around here , are you ?
I got to go where the cosmic winds blow me .
I got to ...
go where no man has gone before .
I 'm a bounty hunter !
Come on , you can 't expect us
to believe this horseshit .
You can believe what you want , son .
All I know is you got to get away from here
while you still can .
Well , there 's something I can agree with .
So walk away .
There you go .
Probably could 've used that lug wrench a little while longer .
Got it .
You should have had your spare tire down here .
Could 've saved you some traveling .
Never know when you 're gonna have a flat tire
on an antique like this .
Are you supposed to be scary ?
Me ?
No .
It ain 't me , it 's them .
I 've seen them .
I 've been seeing them for ...
Look , you believe in monsters ?
- Yeah . - Good . Good .
That 's what I 'm telling you about .
Now , some friends of mine from ...
a long way off ,
they gave me a whole bunch of these .
I only got a couple left ,
but I want you to have one .
Now , if this ever starts to glow bright green ,
that 's the time to watch out for yourself .
And your family .
- Green . - That 's right , green .
Annie ! Johnny !
All aboard !
We really have to go now .
- Yeah , give my regards to Mars . - Don 't be so quick .
You 're not as smart as you think you are .
You can have the rest of my root beer .
Thank you , partner . It 's my favorite .
Johnny , come on now .
Look what I found .
Whoa , what is it ?
I don 't know . It looks like a big electric bullet .
Homemade . He dropped it .
Joshua ! Front and center , now .
- Joshua ? - Josh , please .
- Is that your father ? - Stepfather .
Never , never will we trust you out of our sight again .
When I say five minutes ,
I don 't mean seven , I don 't mean three .
Discipline from now on , young man . Hmm ?
I will not and your mother will not ...
spare anymore rods .
Is he going to get spanked ?
I don 't think his mom is going to let that happen .
Well , Big John , I guess we had some adventure , huh ? !
Dad !
Dad , you should have seen it !
There was this guy , this really strange guy - -
I really don 't care , Annie .
I told you two to stay close , now , didn 't I ?
Look at the two of you ... you 're filthy .
- Johnny , get in the truck . - I know , Dad ,
but he came out of the ground and scared the crap out of us .
He scared the crap out of us .
Miss Sawyer ...
can we please watch our language around Johnny ?
Shit .
Look , honey , I just don 't know what to say to you .
Well , you could say
that you 're not going on the road tomorrow .
You could say that I 'm not old enough
to take care of myself .
Honey , you 're not being fair .
Mr. And Mrs. Menges take real good care of you guys .
They 're like family . Hey ...
it 's the best that I can do .
Besides , you 're a young woman now .
Maybe I don 't want to be a young woman now .
Grover 's Bend ?
What a crock .
You 're listening to Topeka 's
number one country radio station .
Country 107 , KTPK .
Hey , Frank ,
give me a hand with some of this stuff , man .
Absolutely , Mario .
I am the handyman after all .
- You asshole . - I heard that .
Vaya con Dios , Mario .
Four more units to vacate , Jessie ,
and I 'm a rich man .
Hey , you got the elevator fixed .
Frankie .
Hey , not for you , Rosie .
There 's still a one-ton load limit .
Ooh , you ...
Yo , yo , yo . Check your weapons at the door ,
it 's the chick that walks like a man .
Dating outside our species now , huh ?
Oh , very funny .
Very , very funny .
I wasn 't talking to you , Frank .
Yo , Marcia ,
I got a little phone problem .
Maybe you can come down to the basement
and check out my equipment .
Sorry , Frank , I left my microscope upstairs .
Ho-ho ! Ho !
She 's killing me .
Hey , Mario .
I sure am sorry to see you go , my friend .
I just killed two rats this morning .
Rats ? !
Hey , Frank ... rats .
Hey , don 't look at me .
I got to see them to " e-rat-icate " them .
Yo , Jessie , look who 's home .
Something 's wrong .
No brakes !
No brakes ! Hold onto Johnny .
Everybody all right ?
Yeah .
Safe at home .
Oh , man .
I 'm sorry , Mario . No brakes .
Something I can do ?
That 's okay .
Is everybody okay ?
So , uh , Frank ,
you going to give us a hand with this ?
No .
I 'm the maintenance man .
He doesn 't live here anymore .
Muah .
I 'll miss you , Jess .
I 'll be in my office .
Would you mind , uh , clean up this junk ?
The guy 's a waste of protein .
Yeah , but what a snappy dresser .
Oh , Dad , I 'm gonna go say hello to the Menges .
Yeah , but don 't go up empty handed .
You take something with , all right ?
Ladies .
Java .
Fuck . Wh ... ?
What 's this ?
Oh , that 's dlsgustlng . Wha - -
Yeah , you 're next , pal .
Hey , girl .
Oh .
Going down to help Dad ?
I thought I might .
I mean , we got ourselves a loaded truck ,
an unloaded camper , a car wreck ...
- I think they can use my help . - Um , Marcia ?
Are there any jobs down at the phone company ?
What , you need a job ?
Ah , you want Clifford home .
Well , I was just thinking .
We 'll see what we can do .
Yeah , we will .
- Hello ! Hello , Annie . - Hello .
Oh , welcome home , dear . Come in .
Did you have a wonderful trip ?
Dear , say hello to Annie .
They 've just been to the Grand Canyon .
Say , did you know
they just discovered an alien graveyard there ?
- Who did ? - Government .
Secret .
Wait till you taste what I 'm cooking today .
Where 's Johnny ? He 'll love them .
Tell me about your trip , dear .
Oh , yeah .
Well , we froze to death in Arizona ,
saw these Indian caves in Mesa Verde ,
and met this weird lunatic
near Grover 's Bend .
He jumped right out from the ground .
So you had a good time ?
Grover 's Bend ?
I 'm making Mr. Menges ' favorite dish today .
Ham and beans .
Oh , will you and Johnny stay for dinner ?
Oh , no .
It 's our last night together with Dad .
He leaves on the 8 : 15 to Chicago .
Uh , we better save the tarts till later , dear .
I don 't want your father to say I spoiled your dinner ...
again .
Hello , girls .
How you doing , eh ?
Are you a little hungry ?
How about I give you to the old farts upstairs tonight ?
Iris Arms apartment complex ,
Frank Longo at your service .
- Longo , what 's the good news ? - Uh , yo .
Right here . Right here , Mr. Briggs .
I hope you did what I 'm paying you for .
Yes . Well , yes , I did .
Yes , I did .
Mario is history as of right now .
You promised me all of them .
- I lose my Investors ... - Hey .
Wha - -
The way I look at this ,
is that you are making
all the " e ! Giganto " profits off the sale of this shithole ,
not little old moi .
- You listen to me , Frank . - Well ...
Well , maybe it 's time that you get
down here and get involved .
Look , I hired you so I wouldn 't have to get involved .
I 'm not lifting another finger until you pay me for Mario !
You got that ? ! You can take that to the bank !
Balls !
Hello ?
Where are you ?
What are you doing out
without Uncle Frankie 's permission , huh ?
Go back upstairs where you belong !
Work with me !
What this dump needs is a good four alarm fire .
- Dad , dlnner 's getting cold . - Comlng .
I want you to listen to the Menges .
Sometimes I think you don 't listen .
I 'll be back Friday night .
- Oh , toothpaste . - Got it .
And Dad , you really should pack some vitamins , too .
And I want you to help her make beds in the mornings .
She 's not a young woman , you know .
- I 'm done . - Can 't you wait for Dad ?
Mr. M promised me pirate stories .
Ahh !
- Bye . - Bye .
- You be a good boy . - Okay .
- See ya . - See ya .
- Dad . - Hmm ?
What 's going to happen to the Menges ?
I mean , where will they go ?
We 're going to have to move too , you know .
They 'll get us out .
Dad , you 're going to have to deal with this .
You got to think about it , make some decisions .
Annie ...
I 'm going to eat my dinner ,
and then I 'm going to watch some moronic situation comedy ,
and then I 'm going to sleep the sleep of the dead .
Can we worry about this tomorrow , hmm ?
I love my work .
Ow , ow , ow !
Hot ! Hot !
Damn teenagers !
Wh ...
Oh ! Oh , oh ...
Hairballs .
Did you hear something ?
No .
Tell Johnny bedtime , one hour .
That goes for you , too .
Oh , and give this check to Mrs. Menges .
It 's for taking care of you guys .
Tell her I 'll cover the rest of it when I get back .
Dad , remember how much fun we used to have ?
Yeah .
Well , wh - - what was I like then ?
Shorter .
Dad ...
maybe I could go get Johnny
and we could play a game or something .
Honey , give me your battery-powered TV , would you ?
- Who 's there ? - It 's just me .
Laundry night .
I 'm a little spooked tonight , too .
Did you hear screaming before ?
It was probably just Frank .
- What is eating him ? - I don 't know .
Frank 's just naturally repulsive .
Say hello to Mrs. And Mr. Manges for me .
Alright .
Aaah !
Frank ?
I know you 're there . I can hear you breathing .
Talk to me , Frank .
Frank ?
Frank ? Hello ?
All right , Longo , very funny . Enough is enough .
Frank ?
We are not amused .
Frank , try to guess just how close your termination is .
Okay , it 's your funeral , wiseass .
I 'm coming over there and taking care of things myself .
We got another errand to do before we sleep , sport .
Business .
Can 't you just drop me off at home ?
No way , sport .
Someday this pool will be yours .
You 're going to have to learn how to swim in it .
Looks like they 'll have to meet their landlord after all .
See ? Grover 's Bend , 1986 .
Now , you can see the same kind of occurrence two years later ...
1988 .
Even local law enforcement
claims they 've seen space aliens .
One of them supposedly killed a sheriff in the ' 88 encounter .
A sheriff ?
Yes . A sheriff wearing ...
an Easter Bunny suit .
And I 'll bet the aliens were all wearing tuxedos .
Of course ,
he must have been reading the same newspapers as you .
That 's where he got the story in the first place .
Who ? What guy ?
That crazy guy we ran into on vacation .
He actually believes this stuff .
Oh ... I didn 't mean ...
It 's okay .
Look , I 'm sorry .
I guess I 'm still upset over a fight I just had with my dad .
I 'm going to go back downstairs and check on him .
I 'll be back for Johnny in awhile .
Well , John , you still like my stories , don 't you ?
- It 's him ! - Huh ? Who ?
If it glows green ,
that 's the time to watch out for yourself .
Her first frame is a strike .
Michelle led in the earlier rounds in this tournament ,
and was the hot item around
Southern California when it came to sports .
She really was .
Yesterday , in the second round
of match play , Steve , she bowled incredibly .
She had a 300 ...
Hello ?
Frank ?
Frank , is that you ...
or some other rat ?
Well ... huh .
Terrific .
You pervert .
We got varmints .
Frank ,
what in the wild world of Geraldo
is going on down here ?
Oh , my God .
Oh ...
Oh , no ! What is it ? !
Aaah !
There 's more of them !
Get away . Get away .
Oh , no , no ! No , please !
What are these things ? !
Annie ! Annie , help me ! Get it off , get it off !
Get me out of this .
Oh , Annie , hurry !
Hurry , they 're going to come again !
- Rosalle , give me some slack ! - Okay . Owl
It hurts . It hurts .
Oh , Annie ...
Frank .
Oh , Annie , let 's get out of here !
Annie ! Annie !
Oh , Annie !
Come on !
- Help me here . Okay . - Yeah , okay .
Feast your eyes on the future site of Briggs ' Mini Mall .
Nice concept , huh ?
Naming it after yours truly .
But Mom said the court ordered you
to pay them money to move . To relocate .
Not if they move on their own accord , sport .
" Sport . "
There are much simpler ways to sweep and clear .
You 'll see .
You 'll learn .
Come on .
I 'll teach you .
Oh , God , please make this a dream .
Rosalie , come on !
Come on . Dad !
Dad !
- What ? I - That 's right ,
she 'll have a really nice game if she can stay ...
Dad !
- Oh , Dad , it was awful . - There are things . They 're huge !
They 're gigantic . They 're like rats ! Rats !
- No , no , no , badgers . - What happened ?
Badgers . No , Tasmanian devils .
- Slow down ! - Dozens of ' em .
And they attacked me . They had these white fang teeth .
And then - - and they bit me ! They bit me on my leg !
Oh , my God , I 'm bleeding .
Sit over here , Rosie .
Dad , they 're little animals
just like the ones in the paper .
They 've got lots of sharp teeth .
They 're nasty things ... nasty things with sharp teeth .
They 're things from outer space .
You can ask Mr. Manges about it .
Dad , they 're aliens !
Aliens in the basement ?
You have to believe her ! They 're big . They 're huge .
They 're like badger , possums ... they 're big cats .
You got to listen to her , they 're awful !
Rosie , calm down , calm down .
- You just saw a rat . - Dad , will you look at her leg ?
Oh , Rosie .
A rat did this to you ? This is serious .
They 're not rats , Dad .
They got Frank in the basement .
- They got Frank ? - They got Frank !
They got Frank !
Dad ! Oh ...
Dad , come on .
Aaah !
Dad , come on !
What are those things ? !
Go , go , go !
In two tournaments I 've seen her shoot those 300 games .
She can throw the strikes .
- She makes a strike . - Eat that .
God damn it .
You see , sport ?
All kinds of animals follow them around .
These people are animals .
Pretty soon you can 't tell them apart .
The people , the pets ... they 've all got fleas .
This 'll get their attention .
Their attention for what ?
Our little panic ...
casserole .
You think they 're screaming and carrying on now ?
Just wait till I cut off their communication
with their social workers .
Hello ?
That 's funny .
I lost contact with Grover 's Bend .
What did he mean , " Watch out for yourself " ?
Third floor ...
second floor ...
first floor ...
basement .
Who turned out the lights ? !
- Son of a bitch . - Oh , Dad .
How many stairs are in this place anyway ?
Wait , we just went up these stairs .
Oh , I 'm dizzy .
Come on .
What 's your problem , come on .
Oh , I just want to rest .
What the hell are you guys doing down here ?
Marcia ! Marcia , come and help ! They 're passing out .
There are things , they 're like big rats .
Only they bite and ... I forget .
They 're aliens .
Porcupines !
Mrs. Menges ! Mrs. Menges !
Come on , Cliff .
Let me help you . Lean on me .
Up . Up .
Up , that 's it .
- Who are you ? - Marcia .
You know me , Cliff . Come on .
- Marcia ? - Yeah . Come on .
- Up , up . That 's it . - Yeah , okay .
Thank you .
Porcupines ?
Come out , come out , wherever you are .
Your landlord is here to evict you .
Jeez , a rat did that ?
Looks like I 'll have to charge somebody for a new door .
Give me the keys . I 'm gonna wait in the car .
Forget It . We 're In this together .
I thought you cut off all the power .
I did cut off all the power .
Can we just go ?
They must have tapped into the emergency system .
Hello ?
It 's your landlord .
I have matters to discuss .
... Chicken , there 's the wishbone ,
which I 'll cut out .
All this makes perfectly marvelous soup .
You have to get the leg bones out
from the legs and the wing side .
And the way to do that is ...
push the bones through .
And then take ... there 's the ... ball joint
of your roast chicken .
We 'll have our work done in a minute , sport .
Don 't call me " sport . "
You wanna take that off , save everything for soup .
You 're not a crybaby , too , are you , sport ?
- So clip the wings and go , - Huh ?
" Uh ! "
Now ...
I hate you .
I wish you were dead !
Sport ?
Sport !
Hey , come on .
Let me in . Let him go .
Hey.Hey !
Hey , come on . He can 't help being an asshole !
What are you doing ? Hey !
You 're ready to remove the bones .
Hey , come on . He just wants to talk to you !
Leave him alone ! Let him go !
Let him go ! Come on !
Hey , what 's the matter ?
They 've got him . They 're tearing him apart .
- They 're killing him ! - Who ? ! They 've got who ?
Wait . Stop , stop . Step back .
Stay back .
- Come on ! - What 's going on ?
Never mind . Come on ! Go !
This way . Come on .
Let 's go .
No , no , wait ! I can 't just leave him there .
That guy you were with , your dad ?
Stepfather .
Listen ,
I don 't know what the hell is going on down there ,
but I just saw something there .
There 's animals , some kind of hungry things .
I don 't know , but he 's dead , hon .
There 's nothing we can do for him .
- What 's your name ? - Josh .
Okay , Josh ...
Get back !
Oh , look !
- Come on ! - Do you have any more flares ?
Fresh out !
What ?
Let us in !
Close the door !
Josh !
Annie .
Come on , help me move this desk , quick .
- Swing it around that way . - Josh , what are you doing here ?
- I came with her . - Marcia ?
Push it up against the door . Right up tight .
Great . That should hold them .
Josh , how did you get here ?
There 's monsters outside , aren 't there ?
Yeah , there are monsters out there .
- Hey , anybody check the phone ? - It 's dead , like the lights .
You know , I still don 't know what the hell is going on here .
Ain 't no rats , you can be sure of that .
What are you talking about ?
Did you ever see one of these come out of any rat you 've seen ?
Ain 't no rats .
Must be venom ... poison .
They 're here !
I saw the door downstairs , they chewed right through it .
What do you say we barricade the kitchen door ?
What kitchen door ?
Mr. Menges , you don 't have a gun up here
or anything like that ?
I got a great Civil War pistol .
I used to have a frame for It .
I got no powder .
How about a big knife ?
How about a meat cleaver , dear ?
You find anything there , dear ?
No .
Wait .
What 's that ?
Oh . As I recall , that 's a little storage area .
Mr. Menges and I haven 't crawled up there in years .
Josh , come here !
Do you have a footstool or something ?
In the pantry .
Hey , you guys , check this out .
Mrs. Menges , does this connect with the roof ?
I really don 't know where that goes , dear .
You get up there and you crawl ...
crawl that direction ,
and you 'll hit the elevator shaft .
- You don 't know that . - I 'll get the others .
Sure I do . I 've stored stuff up there .
Do you think you guys can climb a ladder ?
No ladder .
Go up a ladder tomorrow .
No .
No tomorrow .
I can 't deal with this anymore , Dad !
Move your ass , now !
Now .
Come on , Clifford .
Hey , hey , we 've been climbing three flights of stairs
ever since that elevator broke down .
Come on . You can do it .
It 's gotten too quiet out there .
I don 't like it .
They 'll just get in some other way .
We got to get out of here !
Rosalie , come on . We got to go . You 're next .
I 'll watch the door .
- Oh , no . - Come on . Up , Roselle .
- Right . - All right .
- Come on , you can do it . - Come on , I 'll help you .
You know ...
if we can make it to the roof ,
I can get to the junction box outside ,
tie into the phone lines , call for help .
- You can do that ? - Hey , I can do anything ...
I work for the phone company .
- Push . - Ow , ow . Ow .
- Up , Rosalie . - Push .
Come on . Go .
- Push , fair Rosie , come on ! - Help .
Push ! Push , Josh .
We 've come this far . Come on , help her .
Look , clear , the quilt that Aunt Carolyn gave us , remember ?
Yeah , I remember . Come on , let 's go .
Everybody be calm , now . Let 's go .
Go !
Go ... quick !
Grab that , quick !
- Go ! - They 're over here !
Josh , come on . Keep going .
Which way do I go ?
Yo , Josh , give me the flashlight .
Kids , here ! Right through there .
Look , you stay with them and try and keep everybody together .
I 'm gonna check out this direction .
Marcia ! Be careful .
Come on , Annie .
Annie .
It won 't open .
Please !
We 're trapped .
Where 's Marcia ?
Oh , damn it .
I 'm lost .
Josh ...
what are you doing here ?
I came here with my stepdad .
We came here to evict you .
I didn 't want to come .
Pretty awful , huh ?
Yeah .
I just can 't believe he 's dead .
Josh ...
my mom died .
Not like your dad ,
but she died .
But I bet you didn 't wish for your mom to die .
I just wish we could go back to this morning .
I just wish we could figure out how to use this thing .
Look ...
if nobody can think of anything better ,
one of us has got to make it to the street and run for help .
The only way I know to get around them things
is this elevator shaft .
Hey .
I got a better idea .
How do you get to the box ?
Redundant cable .
Keeps the lines from blowing down .
It ought to hold my weight long enough for me to ...
get connected .
I 'm down to 119 .
Marcia , you 're going to die out there .
Any calls you want me to make for you ?
Come on . Belay me .
Adios .
Uh-oh .
Okay .
Oh , God .
Josh !
Josh , we 're on fire !
One thing at a time .
Marcia , one thing at a time .
- Oh , my God . Marcia ! - Marcia !
Ohh !
She 's swinging . She 's swinging !
Annie , it 's okay , she 's - -
Oh !
Thank you . Thank you .
Phone . Phone !
Phone , phone .
Let 's go .
Yes . Go . Yes !
Oh , no .
Damn . Damn .
Yeah , yeah .
Go , go !
Yes , yes , yes ! Yes !
No ! No , no .
Yes , yes .
I can do this .
Annie .
I 'm going for help .
It 's okay . I 'm gonna take care of everything .
Annie .
Annie ! Don 't go down there .
That 's too dangerous . You come on back here .
Let somebody else do that .
Second floor .
Hand , foot .
Nothing to it .
Oh !
All right , get back ... get back into the elevator .
I got you , you hear ?
Oh , gee .
It 's jammed .
It 's okay . Sometimes it does this .
What ? !
You came here just in time .
Where 's your family ? Take me to them .
Well , the elevator 's stuck . We have to climb .
How did you get here ?
A gentlemen called me .
A real nice fella .
All right .
- What 's going on ? - I don 't know .
Hold on ! Floor , please ? !
The roof !
Somebody help us out of here .
I 'm stuck .
Hey , it 's you .
Yeah , what 's left of me .
The building is burning downstairs .
We 've got to get on the roof .
Oh .
Don 't look . Don 't ...
be casual but ,
who is that hunk that just came in with your daughter ?
Charlie .
- Hi . - How you doing , partner ?
I guess you were right about those things .
See if you can pry that bullet out of there .
My fingers are too big .
What about Marcia ?
Yes . Yes !
Yes ! Yes ! Yes !
Yes ! Yeah ! Yes !
Please deposit 25 ¢ for the first three minutes .
Damn !
I hate operators .
Quiet .
Everybody quiet .
If you 're quiet , you can hear them moving .
- Annie , my gun . - I 'm trying !
It won 't come out .
All right , keep your eyes on them .
Look ' em in the eye .
They 'll telegraph their every move .
I hate you !
Josh !
You leave my husband alone !
Annie .
Annie ?
Charlie !
Open wide .
We got ' em !
Come on , let 's go !
Mobile Ops 7707 .
Emergency .
Oh , God , no !
Come on , Johnny .
Stay here .
Fire ! Help us !
Can anyone hear me ? !
Please , help us !
Can 't you see us ? !
We 're on fire !
Come over here . Somebody help !
It 's really burning . Up there , can you hear us ? !
- There 's a fire here ! - Is anybody up there ? !
- What are we going to do ? - Hang on . Hang on .
- We 'll be all right . - Please , help us .
You were wonderful .
- Thank you very much . - You saved us all .
Thank you . Thank you very much .
Please , fire ! Come on !
Fire !
Somebody help us ! We 're on fire !
Are you okay ?
Can you stand ?
No , I can 't .
Johnny , get away from the edge !
But Marcia 's down there .
I don 't care . Get over here now !
Listen to me . Get over here !
Look , Annie , look !
Charlie !
- I got you . - Help !
Don 't look down , Johnny .
Annie , don 't let go !
Annie , I 'm slipping .
Hold on , Johnny .
Please , somebody help me !
I got you .
I got you . I got you .
I love you .
Help !
- Charlie ? - Help !
Get help !
Charlie .
Throw me a rope . Get a rope !
Dad , we got to do something .
Oh , no . Oh , no !
Charlie , look out .
Hey ... I hope you 'll let me down easier than that .
Outer space all right .
No doubt about it . We can prove it .
- We could 've proved it except ... - It was all burnt up in there .
Documented proof . All my papers .
Actual physical evidence ... gone .
- Hi . - Hi .
Oh . I 'll be over there , okay ?
- How are you ? - I 'm fine .
So ... how ' bout getting together sometime ,
and doing something normal ?
- Normal like a movie ? - Yeah .
Charlie !
Don 't go .
Uh ...
Listen , partner ,
how 's that crystal doing ?
Yeah .
See ?
There 's no more problem .
- You don 't need me anymore . - Johnny .
Come here a minute .
Bye , Charlie .
Bye , John .
Are you leaving today , Daddy ?
I think I finally got the message
you guys want me to stay close to home .
My uniform 's all burnt up ,
so I think the railroad can get along without me .
Dad , can we survive ?
Well , we 've just been talking about that .
I think I 'll check out those jobs
down at the phone company .
And between the Menges and us ,
we 'll work something out .
- Excuse me . - Yeah .
- I 'm Josh 's mother . - How do you do ?
Josh has told me about all you 've done for him .
And my husband ...
my late husband , he owes you people quite a bit of money .
- He does ? - It 's called a relocation foo .
And I think with that , you 'd be able to stay in a hotel
until we get the place rebuilt .
That Is , If you would be Interested .
We 're interested .
And thank you .
Um ...
Why don 't we introduce ourselves ?
Johnny , where 's your friend from Grover 's Bend ?
Charlie ?
He left .
Just like one of those westerns .
No . No .
All right , you gumballs .
What is that ?
Bounty hunter Charles McFadden , Earth sector ...
you are in violation .
Violation ?
Wait a second . I 'm just killing Critters here .
That is ...
there was a confirmed infestation ...
of Crites .
Charlie .
Is that you in there ?
Charlie , my friend .
Wow .
Wow . It 's great to see you .
And you as well .
You 're looking good .
We just received your bio alert .
Yeah , yeah . What was that all about ?
Specifically , you are prohibited
from terminating any transgalactic lifeform
if it means total extinction of the species .
Oh , yeah . But they 're dangerous .
You taught me how dangerous they are .
Aggression factor is irrelevant .
Those two eggs are the last two eggs .
The intergalactic council has dispatched
a specimen collection pod .
You are instructed to place the eggs
into the receptacle in the pod .
The council is sending a pod here ?
Come on , Ug ...
Good luck , Charlie , my friend .
Yeah , but Ug ...
Ug ! Wait a second . What am I supposed to ...
Ug !